Guide to the Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-1570
  - Rugby Club - Men's, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 125)
  - Rugby Club - Women's, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 126)
  - Russian Choir, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 127)
  - Student Struggle for Oppressed Jewry, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 128)
  - Sailing Club, Dinghy, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 129)
  - Sailing Team, Large Boats, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 130)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 131)
  - Silver Dragon Tae Kwon Do, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 132)
  - Ski Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 133)
  - Society for Careers in Management, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 134)
  - Society for Nutritional Education, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 135)
  - Softball Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 136)
  - Squash Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 137)
  - State of Black America, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 138)
  - TM Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 139)
  - Table Tennis Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 140)
  - Uhuhr Kuumba Dance Ensemble, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 141)
  - Ujamaa, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 142)
  - Ultimate and Disc Club, Men, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 143)
  - Ultimate and Disc Club, Women, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 144)
  - Undergraduate Law Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 145)
  - Volleyball Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 146)
  - Water Polo Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 147)
  - Water Ski Team, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 148)
  - Weightlifting Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 149)
  - West Campus Theatre, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 150)
  - West Indian Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 151)
  - Whistling Shrimp, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 152)
  - Wildife Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 153)
  - Women in Communication, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 154)
  - Women in Health Careers, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 155)
  - World Tae Kwan Do, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 156)
  - Young Israel, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 157)
  - African Students Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 158)
  - Aikido Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 159)
  - American Association Petroleum Geologists, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 160)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 161)
  - Animal Science Grad. Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 162)
  - Anthropology Graduate Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 163)
  - Applied Math Graduate Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 164)
  - Arab Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 165)
  - Asian Peace Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 166)
  - Grad. Black Business Students Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 167)
  - B and PA Doctoral Students Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 168)
  - B and PA Student Committee on Professional Ethics, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 169)
  - Entrepreneurs Club B and PA, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 170)
  - B and PA Information Resource Management Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 171)
  - B and PA International Business Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 172)
  - B and PA Malott Times, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 173)
  - B and PA Marketing Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 174)
  - B and PA Sloan Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 175)
  - Badminton Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 176)
  - Baha'i Assn., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 177)
  - Black Grad. Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 178)
  - Bolivarian Nations Student Comm., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 179)
  - CARP, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 180)
  - China Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 181)
  - Graduate Christian Forum, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 182)
  - Classics Discussion Group, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 183)
  - Cornell Contemporary Ensemble, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 184)
  - Cornell Cricket Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 185)
  - Cyprus Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 186)
  - Development Sociologists GSA, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 187)
  - Ecology and Systems Grad. Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 188)
  - Education Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 189)
  - Environmental Planners at Cornell, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 190)
  - Ethiopian Drought Relief Comm., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 191)
  - Family Housing Advisory Network, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 192)
  - Federation of Alumni from Taiwan, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 193)
  - Folkdancers, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 194)
  - Food Science, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 195)
  - French Speaking Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 196)
  - Gamma Alpha, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 197)
  - Grads for Grads, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 198)
  - Holistic Health Study Group, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 199)
  - Housing Issues Group, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 200)
  - Human Service Studies Group, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 201)
  - India Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 202)
  - International Assoc. of Camel Breeders, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 203)
  - Jitterbug Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 204)
  - Jugatae, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 205)
  - Korean Grad. Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 206)
  - Landscape Architects, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 207)
  - Law: Am. Indian Law Students Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 208)
  - Law: Asian Am. Law Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 209)
  - Law: Environmental, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 210)
  - Law: Legal Aid Society, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 211)
  - Law: Public Interest, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 212)
  - Law: National Lawyers Guild, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 213)
  - Grad. Literature Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 214)
  - Mexican Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 215)
  - MECA, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 216)
  - Mu Sigma Rho, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 217)
  - Natural Rescues Grad. Student Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 218)
  - Nov. 11 Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 219)
  - Grad. Nutrition Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 220)
  - Olericulture, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 221)
  - Operations Research, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 222)
  - Organization of Cornell Planners, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 223)
  - Peace Studies/Peace Science, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 224)
  - Plant Pathology Grad. Student Council, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 225)
  - Regional Science Students Assoc., 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 226)
  - Sage Hall Dorm Council, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 227)
  - Scandinavian Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 228)
  - Ithaca Scottish Country Dancers, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 229)
  - Singapore Club, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 230)
  - Grad. Sociology Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 231)
  - Sri Lanka Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 232)
  - Taiwanese Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 233)
  - Venezuelan Student Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 234)
  - Student Chapter of the American Veterans Medical Association, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 235)
  - Vet: American Association of Equine Practitioners, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 236)
  - Vet: American Association of Zoo Vets, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 237)
  - Wives, Cornell Student, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 238)
  - Women in International Development, 1983-1984 (Box 37-1-1570 - 12, Folder 239)
  - Academic Calendars and Calendar of Events (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Delta Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 2)
  - Chi Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 3)
  - Concert Policy (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Policy (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 5)
  - Delta Upsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 6)
  - Division of Campus Life Reorganization (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 7)
  - Drug and Alcohol Use at Cornell University (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 8)
  - Fraternities (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 9)
  - Fraternities - Summer Ground Maintenance (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 10)
  - Fraternity: Alpha Chi Rho (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 11)
  - Fraternity: Alpha Phi Omega-Gamma (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 12)
  - Fraternity: Alpha Tau Omega (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 13)
  - Fraternity: Alpha Zeta (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 14)
  - Fraternity: Beta Sigma Rho (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 15)
  - Fraternity: Beta Theta Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 16)
  - Fraternity: Chi Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 17)
  - Fraternity: Chi Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 18)
  - Fraternity: Delta Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 19)
  - Fraternity: Delta Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 20)
  - Fraternity: Delta Tau Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 21)
  - Fraternity: Gamma Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 22)
  - Fraternity: Kappa Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 23)
  - Fraternity: Kappa Delta Rho (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 24)
  - Fraternity: Kappa Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 25)
  - Fraternity: Lambda Chi Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 26)
  - Fraternity: Lambda Sigma Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 27)
  - Fraternity: Omega Tau Sigma - includes Men of Veterinary Medicine Calendar (2005) (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 28)
  - Fraternity: Phi Alpha Omega (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 29)
  - Fraternity: Phi Delta Theta (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 30)
  - Fraternity: Phi Epsilon Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 31)
  - Fraternity: Phi Gamma Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 32)
  - Fraternity: Phi Kappa Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 33)
  - Fraternity: Phi Kappa Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 34)
  - Fraternity: Phi Kappa Tau (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 35)
  - Fraternity: Phi Sigma Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 36)
  - Fraternity: Phi Sigma Kappa (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 37)
  - Fraternity: Pi Kappa Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 38)
  - Fraternity: Pi Kappa Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 39)
  - Fraternity: Psi Upsilon, 1979 (Box 37-1-1570 - 56, Folder 40)
  - Fraternity: Psi Upsilon, 1979-1985 (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 41)
  - Fraternity: Seal and Serpent (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 42)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 43)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 44)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Mu Chi (Student Mgmt. Corporation) (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 45)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Nu (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 46)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 47)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Phi Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 48)
  - Fraternity: Sigma Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 49)
  - Fraternity: Tau Epsilon Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 50)
  - Fraternity: Tau Kappa Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 51)
  - Fraternity: Theta Delta Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 52)
  - Fraternity: Triangle (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 53)
  - Fraternity Recommendation #5: Membership Selection Prodecures during Rush Forms (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 54)
  - Fraternity Recommendation #5: Report on Compliance (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 55)
  - Fraternity Recommendation #5: Saperston Report (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 56)
  - Fraternity Recommendation #5: Statement of Compliance (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 57)
  - Fraternity - University (Cornell) (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 58)
  - Fraternity: Colonization Procedures (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 59)
  - FSSRB General (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 60)
  - FSSRB History (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 61)
  - General Info. (Rush Schedule, #'s, and Guidelines) (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 62)
  - Graduate Coordinating Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 63)
  - Greek Early Advisement and Referral System (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 64)
  - Group Housing Plan (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 65)
  - IFC and Fraternity present and former officers (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 66)
  - IFC - Miscellaneous (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 67)
  - IFC/Panhel Judicial Board (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 68)
  - Insurance Certifications (Box 37-1-1570 - 57, Folder 69)
  - Intercollegiate Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 70)
  - Intercollegiate Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 71)
  - Kappa Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 72)
  - Kappa Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 73)
  - Kappa Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 74)
  - Leadership Issue (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 75)
  - Motivation Ideas (Group Management) (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 76)
  - National Panhellenic Conference (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 77)
  - Office of the DOS - Campus Affairs Info. Reports (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 78)
  - Order of Omega Greek Leadership Conference (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 79)
  - Panhellenic Conference (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 80)
  - Phi Gamma Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 81)
  - Policies and Procedures (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 82)
  - Program Budget and Budget Planning Documents (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 83)
  - Psi Upsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 84)
  - Report on Fraternities (various schools) (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 85)
  - Resource (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 86)
  - Scheduling Coordination and Activities Review Board (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 87)
  - Sororities (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 88)
  - Sorority: Alpha Epsilon Phi (Defunct) (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 89)
  - Sorority: Kappa Delta (Reestablishment) (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 90)
  - Sorority: Kappa Kappa Gamma (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 91)
  - Sorority: Kappa Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 92)
  - Student Agencies, Inc. (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 93)
  - Student Organization Directory (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 94)
  - Title IV and Sex Discrimination (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 95)
  - Univ. Relationship with fraternities and sororities - Prelim. info. (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 96)
  - Women's Issues (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 97)
  - Zeta Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 58, Folder 98)
  - Alumni Assoc., 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 1)
  - Counseling - including Gray Sheet (1984-1985), 1982-1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 2)
  - Cult, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 3)
  - Human Relations Training, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol and Drug Education, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 5)
  - Acquaintance Rape, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 6)
  - Leadership Conference, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 7)
  - Legal Liability, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 8)
  - Off-Campus Housing Survey, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 9)
  - Collegetown Neighborhood, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 10)
  - Parents Weekend, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 11)
  - Pledge Activities, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 12)
  - Programs to Eliminate Hazing, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 13)
  - Publicity, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 14)
  - Rush, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 15)
  - Sexism, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 16)
  - Fiji, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 17)
  - Fiji, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 17a)
  - Fiji, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 17b)
  - Fiji, 1989 (Box 37-1-1570 - 59, Folder 17c)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Gamma Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 4)
  - Alpha Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 5)
  - Chi Omega (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 6)
  - Delta Delta Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 7)
  - Delta Gamma (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 8)
  - Delta Phi Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 9)
  - Delta Sigma Theta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 10)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 11)
  - Kappa Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 12)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 13)
  - Pi Beta Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 14)
  - Zeta Phi Beta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 15)
  - Alpha Xi Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 16)
  - Phi Sigma Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 17)
  - Sigma Delta Tau (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 18)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 19)
  - Sigma Kappa (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 20)
  - Sorority Chapter Advisors (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 21)
  - Rush Statistic (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 22)
  - Panhel - Rush (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 23)
  - Sorority Houseparents (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 24)
  - Panhel - Minutes (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 25)
  - Panhel - Social (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 26)
  - Panhel - Service (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 27)
  - Panhel - Speakers (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 28)
  - Panhel - Budget (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 29)
  - Panhel - Constitution and By-laws (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 30)
  - Panhel - Miscellaneous (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 31)
  - Panhel - Former Officers (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 32)
  - Panhel - Extension (Box 37-1-1570 - 60, Folder 33)
  - Acacia (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 1)
  - Alpha Chi Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Delta Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 4)
  - Alpha Gamma Rho (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 5)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 6)
  - Alpha Sigma Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 7)
  - Alpha Tau Omega (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 8)
  - Alpha Zeta (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 9)
  - Beta Theta Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 10)
  - Chi Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 11)
  - Chi Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 12)
  - Delta Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 13)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 14)
  - Delta Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 15)
  - Delta Tau Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 16)
  - Delta Upsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 17)
  - Kappa Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 18)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 19)
  - Kappa Delta Rho (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 20)
  - Kappa Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 21)
  - Lambda Chi Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 22)
  - Lambda Upsilon Lambda (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 23)
  - Omega Psi Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 24)
  - Phi Beta Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 25)
  - Phi Delta Theta (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 26)
  - Phi Gamma Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 27)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 28)
  - Phi Psi 500 (Box 37-1-1570 - 61, Folder 29)
  - Phi Kappa Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 1)
  - Phi Kappa Tau (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 2)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 3)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 4)
  - Pi Kappa Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 5)
  - Psi Upsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 6)
  - Seal and Serpent (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 7)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 8)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 9)
  - Sigma Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 10)
  - Sigma Chi Delta (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 11)
  - Sigma Nu (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 12)
  - Sigma Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 13)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 14)
  - Sigma Pi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 15)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 16)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 17)
  - Theta Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 18)
  - Theta Delta Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 19)
  - Zeta Beta Tau (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 20)
  - Zeta Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 21)
  - IFC - Correspondence (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 22)
  - IFC - Judicial (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 23)
  - IFC - Rush (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 24)
  - IFC - Social (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 25)
  - IFC - Minutes (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 26)
  - IFC - Work Study (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 27)
  - IFC - Budget (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 28)
  - IFC - Faculty (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 29)
  - IFC - Community Services (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 30)
  - IFC - Chapters (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 31)
  - IFC - Colonization (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 32)
  - IFC - Constitution/By-laws (Box 37-1-1570 - 62, Folder 33)
  - Alcohol Registration (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 1)
  - AFA (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 2)
  - Alert (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 3)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee on Alcohol Policy (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 4)
  - Black Greek Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 5)
  - Bonfires (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 6)
  - Civitas (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 7)
  - CURP - Tax (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 8)
  - Deanery - Budget (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 9)
  - Deanery Priorities/Goals (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Notification (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 12)
  - Fraternities and Sororities Seeking Houses (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 13)
  - Fraternity Research (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 14)
  - Greek Task Force (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 15)
  - Hazing Policy (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 16)
  - IFC - PH Stats. and Rosters (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 17)
  - Ithaca Community Issues (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 18)
  - Judicial (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 19)
  - Job Description (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 20)
  - Major Events Planning (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 22)
  - NIC (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 23)
  - NPHC (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 24)
  - NPHC Fraternities and Sororities (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 25)
  - Order of Omega (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 26)
  - Public Safety (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 27)
  - SMC (Box 37-1-1570 - 63, Folder 28)
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-1553
  - Small Living Unit Council, 1967-1968 (Box 37-1-1553 - 1, Folder 1)
  - Head Resident material, 1961-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 1, Folder 2)
  - Intersession Program, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 1, Folder 3)
  - Manual for Head Residents, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 1, Folder 4)
  - Manual for Head Residents, 1968-1969 (another copy) (Box 37-1-1553 - 1, Folder 5)
  - Reference Book for Residential Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 37-1-1553 - 1, Folder 6)
  - Registration: student groups - speakers - events, 1970-1972 (Box 37-1-1553 - 2, Folder 1)
  - Inter-university evaluation teams (R. Siggelkow), 1960-1962 (Box 37-1-1553 - 2, Folder 2)
  - Allee Committee [Housing and Dining Commission] - drafts and writing assignments, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 2, Folder 3)
  - Allee Committee [Housing and Dining Commission] - correspondence and minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 2, Folder 4)
  - Dining, 1970 (Box 37-1-1553 - 2, Folder 5)
  - Noyes Center, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 2, Folder 6)
  - Housing and Dining materials, 1968-1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 1)
  - Housing - general, 1966-1971 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 2)
  - Women's residence requirement, 1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 3)
  - Tension in dorms, 1969 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 4)
  - Mid-year staff reports, January 1970 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 5)
  - Housing issues and policies, 1969-1971 (Box 37-1-1553 - 3, Folder 6)